(Howard:)No!
(Sheldon:)This might be a good time
to point out, Howard,
(Sheldon:)that friendship requires
a certain give and take.
(Sheldon:)Hold the door.
(Doctor:)Mr. Wolowitz?
- Is she okay?
- It wasn't a heart attack.
(Doctor:)She's awake, she's
resting comfortably--
(Doctor:)we're still
running a few tests.
(Howard:)Can I see her?
(Doctor:)Actually, she said,
and I quote,
she'd "like to see the
little Catholic girl first."
(Bernadette:)Me? Why me?
(Howard:)Jews have been asking
that for centuries.
(Howard:)There's no real good answer.
(Penny:)Okay, well,
wish me luck.
(Howard:)Don't worry,
you'll be fine.
(Howard:)Let's just hide Mr. Cross.
(Howard:)If it touches her, it burns.
(Doctor:)You brought a Catholic girl
home to your mother?
(Bernadette:)Yeah.
(Doctor:)Why don't I write you a
prescription for Xanax.